{
    "id": "b1d9a31361c2404f80160702561b3938",
    "title": "Identify The Tenses",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have been working on my computer for six hours.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Present continuous",
                "Past continuous",
                "Present perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She has lived in this street for ten years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Simple past",
                "Present perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I finished the project yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple past",
                "Simple present",
                "Present perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What are you doing there?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Present continuous",
                "Present perfect",
                "Past continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She had not realized that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Present perfect",
                "Past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Susan will be joining us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Present continuous",
                "Future continuous tense",
                "Past continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever been to Australia?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Present perfect tense",
                "Past perfect tense"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This house had been destroyed by the fire.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Present perfect",
                "Past perfect",
                "Simple past"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys were severely reprimanded by their teacher.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple past tense",
                "Present perfect",
                "Past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I had been working in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Present continuous",
                "Past continuous",
                "Past perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She will come with us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple present",
                "Simple future",
                "Present perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "By this time tomorrow, I will have finished working on it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple future",
                "Future continuous",
                "Future perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}